IGOR PAKHOLKOV

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER



Telegram:
@CoderGosha
Email:

coder.gosha@gmail.com Web Site:

https://codergosha.com

SKILS:

C#

- .NET Core
- EF Core
- Dapper
- SQL
- Миграция

.NET Framework

- -> .NET Core
- Web API
- async/await
- Andriod
- Smart Watch

PYTHON

- Django
- Django-rest
- Web Api
- WebSocket
- asyncio
- QT
- Selenuim

DATABASE

- Oracle Database
- MSSQL
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- SQLite

PROFILE

I'm a Lead Software Engineer on C# and Python and I have more than 8 years of experience. I participated in the development of manufacturing real-time system tracking (level 2). I did integration with a manufacturing microcontroller (like scales). I developed part of the metal accounting system. I supported and added new features to OPC Core (OPC Unified Architecture. NET Standard).

Now, I'm developing a high load backend for a parcel delivery system.

Current projects use .NET Core and ASP .Core. I have big experience of a migration from .NET Framework to .NET Core.

Prototypes and pet projects I write in python (FastAPI, Django, Flask) and sometimes in Monkey C.

I'm looking for the role of Senior Backend Developer with stack: C#, .NET Core and development prospects in Team/Tech Lead

EXPERIENCE

Senior backend developer, Engy — 2020 - 2022

I'm developing a high load backend for a parcel delivery system.

- I'm doing integration with partners API. I ported and migrated the parcel delivery system from ASP .NET to ASP .NET Core.
- · Integration tests, performance optimization.
- I'm actively supporting core for Windows (IIS + Docker + MSSQL) and Linux (nginx + docker + postgreSQL).

Stack: TFS, Git. ASP .Core, EF Core, Dapper, MSSQL, PostgreeSQL, Docker

Pilot client project for postamat on python. The client used QT and worked on an embodied system (raspberry pi). Device management, bank acquiring, receiving and delivering parcels.

Stack: Python, Sqlite, PySide, Raspberry Pi

Senior software engineer, PSS. Software — 2018-2020

I supported and added new features to OPC Core (OPC Unified Architecture. NET Standard).

- I ported and migrated OPC Core from .NET Framework (Windows + MSSQL) to .NET Core (cross-platform).
- And I developed a microservice for the tickets bay system on ASP .Core.
- The company used Microsoft Azure for building and deployment.

Stack: TFS, Git. ASP .Core, EF Core, MSSQL, PostgreeSQL, Docker, RabbitMQ

CI/CD

- Docker
- Docker Compose
- TFS
- GitHub
- Gogs/Drone

HARDWARE & VIRTUALIZATION

- DigitalOcean
- Azure
- VirtualBox
- Embedded Systems (Raspberry Pi, ТСД)
- Garmin Watch

LANGUAGES

- Russian native
- English B2

Software engineer, Data Center Automatization Company — 2014-2018

I participated in the development of manufacturing real-time system tracking (level 2) Real time collection data, analysis manufacturing processes, integration with manufacturing microcontrollers. I developed tracking systems modules. I developed and supported a data collection system from weighing devices and controllers.

Stack: Git, SVN ASP.NET, EF, MVC, WCF, REST, SOAP, SQL, MS SQL, Oracle, UnitTests, JavaScript, C#, C++, HTML, CSS

EDUCATION

Software engineer, Cherepovets State University — 2009-2014

Software for Computers and Computer-Aided Systems

Dissertation: Data Scales - data collection system from weighing devices and controllers